<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
		<!--	created with www.mysitemapgenerator.com	-->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
	<channel>
		<title>Static Apartment Therapy</title>
		<link><![CDATA[http://static.apartmenttherapy.com]]></link>
		<description>The latest international news from Static Apartment Therapy, featuring top stories from around the Lifestyle and breaking news, as it happens.</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 19:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
		<generator>MySitemapGenerator (www.mysitemapgenerator.com)</generator>

		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">1530984281</guid>
			<title>The hardships and joys of the Himalayan expedition cannot be explained to others</title>
			<link>http://static.apartmenttherapy.com/The-hardships-and-joys-of-the-Himalayan-expedition-cannot-be-explained-to-others.html</link>
			<author>Administrator</author>
			<category>Site News</category>
			<description>The latest international news from Static Apartment Therapy, featuring top stories from around the Lifestyle and breaking news, as it happens.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>The hardships and joys of the Himalayan expedition cannot be explained to others</h2><p><img src="http://static.apartmenttherapy.com/images/Himalayan.JPG"></p><p>Annapurna Basecamp from Pokhara, Nepal—a 10-day trek in all. The path is difficult, but full of otherLifestylely beauty. This beauty of Himalayan nature makes you forget the difficulty of reaching the destination. How much more is that visual! Iftekharul Islam has walked on this mountain path in May . He is writing that experience serially. Read the eighth episode today</p><p>It doesn't take long to pack everything back at camp. I am ready with my bag and backpack around six o'clock after breakfast. I asked guide Tej, can't we go out now without having breakfast here so early in the morning? Tej said, it is a very good decision. From here we will reach Machhapuchar basecamp after one and a half hour walk. Breakfast can be served there. Almost all those starting the return trek from here today will spend the night at Dovan or Bambu. If we leave now and can walk at a normal pace, we will end the day by going to Lower Sinuwa if possible. The next day will be a relatively short trek. I will reach Jhinu in three to four hours. There are hot springs. Beautiful green hills around.</p><p>Jhinu is the next day's goal, but think about it later. Now leave Annapurna Basecamp and start our journey back. All around is sparkling white from last night's snowfall. The dazzling whiteness of the morning sun fell on it. I didn't know it could be so brightly sunny all around at half past six in the morning. The sunglasses that I have been wearing since yesterday morning, I put them on again this morning. Sometimes I need glasses, but I can't take off my sunglasses. At this height of the mountain, walking in such snow country requires category III or IV sunglasses with polarized lenses. These sunglasses allow only 8 to 10 percent of light to enter.</p><p>After a short walk I realized that it was a very ambitious goal and a bold decision to trek from here to Lower Sinuwa in one day. Descending the mountain path is not always easy. At the time of descent, you have to climb uphill in many places. And the pressure on the front of the foot, especially on the big toe, when going downhill over the rocks, can sometimes take a very bad clinical form.</p><p>I already walk slowly. When the pain in the toe becomes excruciating, my walking pace becomes very slow. My toenails have been damaged before after the trek. Same situation this time too. Tej does not understand why he is walking so slowly. He can never walk at a normal pace when he comes with me. So I feel a little bad for him. I don't feel like eating anything at lunch today. But how can I walk such a long way without playing enough? After a while, everyone eats protein bars and dates out of the backpack.</p><p>After lunch break, I took off my boots and socks and applied Move Spray on both big toes. The pain is slightly reduced. It is very temporary. However, I can walk for a while because of the temporary relief. Then the pain comes back. It was difficult while walking, but I did not realize how much damage was done to the feet, especially the toes.</p><p>In the afternoon it was realized that I would not be able to reach Lower Sinuwa before evening. The path to be passed in the darkness of the evening is the most difficult part of the day. One hour steepest ascent and half an hour steepest descent. In the end, I noticed that it was getting less difficult to climb higher. Going down is more difficult. I finally turned around and went down one step at a time as my toes hurt while stepping forward. Tej went some distance and stood for me.</p><p>Already away from the towns and remote mountain paths in the lonely silence met with himself anew; Various thoughts started buzzing in the mind. No one will ever be told how many thoughts come to mind while walking here alone all day. Met many trekkers on the way till noon. Hi, hello, namaste—such greetings are exchanged. After noon, the trekking route became uncrowded. Against the background of such a big mountain, I am all alone in the peaceful silence.</p><p>Mountain peaks, some unfulfilled dreams and unknown thirsts pull me. After reaching the goal, I came back with wonderful memories. Can't even walk very fast. He felt a little upset because of the severe pain in his legs and the very slow pace. I try to remove that sadness with the memory of coming to see Annapurna. Now no matter how hard it is, I have reached another most beautiful destination of the Himalayas, I have seen the magnificent Annapurna. A peace of mind.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 19:48:36 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">1515866315</guid>
			<title>Find out about 10 popular camping sites in the country</title>
			<link>http://static.apartmenttherapy.com/Find-out-about-10-popular-camping-sites-in-the-country.html</link>
			<author>Administrator</author>
			<category>Site News</category>
			<description>The latest international news from Static Apartment Therapy, featuring top stories from around the Lifestyle and breaking news, as it happens.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Find out about 10 popular camping sites in the country</h2><p><img src="http://static.apartmenttherapy.com/images/camping.JPG"></p><p>Winter is the ideal time for camping. Adventure-seeking travelers often set up their tents and set out for a new destination at this time. You can also go out—alone or with a group. If you don't have your own camping equipment, you can find a camping site. But before camping, consider safety, location, natural beauty. Monirul Islam is looking for 10 popular camping sites</p><p>The hill in Miringa range is called Marayan Thang. Ali Kadam in Bandarban is very popular for camping among nature worshippers. Standing at the top, as far as the eye can see, only hills wrapped in green. In the morning, the distant mountains are covered with white finfin clouds. The sunrise viewing experience from here is unique. As the sun rises, the entire valley is bathed in golden light. As time goes on, the shape of the hilly nature changes moment by moment.</p><p>Despite the name, Kukri-Mukri is actually an island. This island of Bhola Charfashion lies in the estuary of the Meghna and Tentulia rivers bordering the Bay of Bengal. Char kukri-mukri dense forest and breath-taking trees will seem to have entered the depths of the Sundarbans. Forests and water bodies make it easy to forget the complexities of urban life. And hours can be spent looking at the starry sky in the stillness of the night.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 19:48:34 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">2385492899</guid>
			<title>How I traveled two countries with one ticket</title>
			<link>http://static.apartmenttherapy.com/How-I-traveled-two-countries-with-one-ticket.html</link>
			<author>Administrator</author>
			<category>Site News</category>
			<description>The latest international news from Static Apartment Therapy, featuring top stories from around the Lifestyle and breaking news, as it happens.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>How I traveled two countries with one ticket</h2><p><img src="http://static.apartmenttherapy.com/images/travel.JPG"></p><p>Annapurna Basecamp from Pokhara, Nepal—a 10-day trek in all. The path is difficult, but full of otherLifestylely beauty. This beauty of Himalayan nature makes you forget the difficulty of reaching the destination. How much more is that visual! Iftekharul Islam has walked on this mountain path in May . He is writing that experience serially. Read the eighth episode today</p><p>It doesn't take long to pack everything back at camp. I am ready with my bag and backpack around six o'clock after breakfast. I asked guide Tej, can't we go out now without having breakfast here so early in the morning? Tej said, it is a very good decision. From here we will reach Machhapuchar basecamp after one and a half hour walk. Breakfast can be served there. Almost all those starting the return trek from here today will spend the night at Dovan or Bambu. If we leave now and can walk at a normal pace, we will end the day by going to Lower Sinuwa if possible. The next day will be a relatively short trek. I will reach Jhinu in three to four hours. There are hot springs. Beautiful green hills around.</p><p>Jhinu is the next day's goal, but think about it later. Now leave Annapurna Basecamp and start our journey back. All around is sparkling white from last night's snowfall. The dazzling whiteness of the morning sun fell on it. I didn't know it could be so brightly sunny all around at half past six in the morning. The sunglasses that I have been wearing since yesterday morning, I put them on again this morning. Sometimes I need glasses, but I can't take off my sunglasses. At this height of the mountain, walking in such snow country requires category III or IV sunglasses with polarized lenses. These sunglasses allow only 8 to 10 percent of light to enter.</p><p>After a short walk I realized that it was a very ambitious goal and a bold decision to trek from here to Lower Sinuwa in one day. Descending the mountain path is not always easy. At the time of descent, you have to climb uphill in many places. And the pressure on the front of the foot, especially on the big toe, when going downhill over the rocks, can sometimes take a very bad clinical form.</p><p>I already walk slowly. When the pain in the toe becomes excruciating, my walking pace becomes very slow. My toenails have been damaged before after the trek. Same situation this time too. Tej does not understand why he is walking so slowly. He can never walk at a normal pace when he comes with me. So I feel a little bad for him. I don't feel like eating anything at lunch today. But how can I walk such a long way without playing enough? After a while, everyone eats protein bars and dates out of the backpack.</p><p>After lunch break, I took off my boots and socks and applied Move Spray on both big toes. The pain is slightly reduced. It is very temporary. However, I can walk for a while because of the temporary relief. Then the pain comes back. It was difficult while walking, but I did not realize how much damage was done to the feet, especially the toes.</p><p>In the afternoon it was realized that I would not be able to reach Lower Sinuwa before evening. The path to be passed in the darkness of the evening is the most difficult part of the day. One hour steepest ascent and half an hour steepest descent. In the end, I noticed that it was getting less difficult to climb higher. Going down is more difficult. I finally turned around and went down one step at a time as my toes hurt while stepping forward. Tej went some distance and stood for me.</p><p>Already away from the towns and remote mountain paths in the lonely silence met with himself anew; Various thoughts started buzzing in the mind. No one will ever be told how many thoughts come to mind while walking here alone all day. Met many trekkers on the way till noon. Hi, hello, namaste—such greetings are exchanged. After noon, the trekking route became uncrowded. Against the background of such a big mountain, I am all alone in the peaceful silence.</p><p>Mountain peaks, some unfulfilled dreams and unknown thirsts pull me. After reaching the goal, I came back with wonderful memories. Can't even walk very fast. He felt a little upset because of the severe pain in his legs and the very slow pace. I try to remove that sadness with the memory of coming to see Annapurna. Now no matter how hard it is, I have reached another most beautiful destination of the Himalayas, I have seen the magnificent Annapurna. A peace of mind.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 19:48:35 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">290384485</guid>
			<title>Privacy Policy</title>
			<link>http://static.apartmenttherapy.com/privacy-policy.html</link>
			<author>Administrator</author>
			<category>Site News</category>
			<description>The latest international news from Static Apartment Therapy, featuring top stories from around the Lifestyle and breaking news, as it happens.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>Privacy Policy</h2><p>Suggested text: When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.</p><p>An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.</p><p>Suggested text: If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.</p><p>Suggested text: If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.</p><p>If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.</p><p>When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.</p><p>If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.</p><p>Suggested text: Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.</p><p>These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 19:52:43 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">2536745403</guid>
			<title>What's exciting at Foy's Lake Basecamp in Chittagong?</title>
			<link>http://static.apartmenttherapy.com/article.html</link>
			<author>Administrator</author>
			<category>Site News</category>
			<description>The latest international news from Static Apartment Therapy, featuring top stories from around the Lifestyle and breaking news, as it happens.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<h2>What's exciting at Foy's Lake Basecamp in Chittagong?</h2><p>Chittagong is the favorite destination of many because it has both mountains and sea. Along with nature and heritage sightings, adventure seekers can keep Foy's Lake Basecamp on their list. What is there? Fahim Al Samad reports</p><p>Surrounded by trees. Among them is a lake of calm blue water on the mountain. You can see wild deer or rabbits while taking a boat on that lake. Along with the natural beauty, you can enjoy all the thrilling rides. Foy's Lake is the name of this recreation center built on 336 acres of hilly area of Chittagong city.</p><p>'Basecamp' was launched at Foy's Lake this year. This joint venture of Concord Group of Companies and Basecamp Adventures Limited has various activities to increase physical and mental skills. A group activity 'Tree Top Activity' centered around a few trees. Five obstacle 'on ground activities' for thrill seekers. 'Team building game' for leadership development. There are also opportunities for kayaking in the lake water. Archery to train the bow and arrow. You can go from one side of the lake to the other side by 'water zip line'. There are also giant swings and hammocks for swinging.</p><p>You can come to Chittagong from anywhere in the country by CNG-powered auto-rickshaw or car and go to Foy's Lake. Basecamp activities can also be done individually here, but day-long activities and overnight packages are more popular.</p><p>The path to the basecamp along the lake. Reception and restaurant at the entrance. You can get some refreshment here to get rid of travel fatigue. After that, the mountain road is divided into two parts. If you follow the straight path, you will reach 'Camping Hill'. And going up to the right is 'Activity Hill'. This hill is decorated with several types of exciting activities. At the beginning there is the 'Zip Line'. But do these activities at the end. From there, you will see tree top activities and on ground activities. In these two exercises, physical skills as well as mental skills should be introduced. Another exciting addition is the giant swing. It is several times longer than a normal swing. You will be pulled off the ground at least 10 feet and released. You will enjoy the beauty of Chittagong city from the top of the hill while swinging.</p><p>Now let's go to the zip line, one of the attractions of the camp. Hang on the wire and move from side to side over the water of the lake. Children's activities next to Camp Hill for the little ones. After all the activities and lunch, you can spend a nice afternoon lying in the giant hammock. Or you can end the day by kayaking on the lake. The whole day will cost 3 thousand rupees per person. With food from morning to evening.</p><p>The true beauty of Basecamp emerges at night. A thrilling atmosphere is created by the call of crickets and the barking of foxes. In the evening, the campfire was lit on the shore of the lake. There are groups of people sitting there singing. If you want, you can spend the whole night sitting here. Or you can go back to the tent and rest. If you want light trekking in moonlight you can go to 'Into the Wild' hill. A winding path of about three kilometers through the forest. You can forget all the tiredness of the day and walk along this path surrounded by nature in the moonlight. If you add camping with all the activities of the day, it will cost 7 thousand rupees per person. All meals will be available till next morning. Keeping in mind the safety of the tourists, there are a few skilled instructors present during each thrilling activity. Basecamp site manager Nazmul Waheed said there are two levels of security for the safety of tourists. All arrangements are made here to provide maximum security and service to the tourists.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Dec 2023 19:48:32 GMT</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>